<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<projects>
    <project>
        <title>Ace Training</title>
        <description>This is a project from University that was a course/education/moodle style website, where users who created an account would need to
            accepted by an admin. Accepted users could sign up for a course, and if accepted by the courses tutor would be able to have access and see the
            resources (quizzes, documents etc.) uploaded by the tutor. Tutors had the abilitiy to set when resources were available from and to, aswell as
            the ability to create custom quizzes and see the scores of the users who took them.
        </description>
        <summary>Education/Course Resource Website</summary>
        <technologies>PHP, BootstrapCSS, JavaScript, HTML</technologies>
        <image_url>./Screenshots/AceTraining/Ace Training Image.jpg</image_url>
        <project_url>https://github.com/Ukelt/Portfolio/tree/main/AceTraining/LoginTest</project_url>
    </project>
    <project>
        <title>SociArt</title>
        <description>A social media like app. An app that is supposed to support more collaborative art work, and with a bigger push towards an art based 
            social media website. Users can post like you would on a normal social media website, including uploading up to 4 media posts, but they can also
            create a room which has a HTML5 canvas they can draw in, and then post it. Users can also comment on posts, and like them. 
        </description>
        <summary>Social Media Site</summary>
        <technologies>React, Nodejs, HTML, JavaScript, CSS</technologies>
        <image_url>./Screenshots/SociArt/SociArt SC.png</image_url>
        <project_url>https://github.com/Ukelt/SociArt</project_url>
    </project>
    <project>
        <title>HabitTracker</title>
        <description>An android app for keeping tracks of habits, uses a daily, weekly a monthly approach, allows custom creation of habits, and lets user delete them. </description>
        <summary>Android Habit Tracker App</summary>
        <technologies>Java</technologies>
        <image_url>./Screenshots/HabitTracker/Black.jpg</image_url>
        <project_url>https://github.com/Ukelt/HabitTracker</project_url>
    </project>
</projects>
